

PROFILE

I am a recent graduate full stack developer with a year of experience in front-end development using HTML CSS, JavaScript (React), back-end using Java creating independent projects. Also, I have 6+ years of business analyst experience in healthcare sector. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+358466214003

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nupurbhardwaj-807108180/

EMAIL:

nupur.7bhardwaj@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/nupur7bhardwaj

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Reading Travelling Scuba Diving Hiking Exploring Cuisines

NUPUR BHARDWAJ

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer LukuLab

2022-Present

Collaborated in a team of three to develop a web-based tool with frontend and backend technologies for dyslexic's children learning at - LukuLab (www.LukuLab.com) a Startup company.

I worked with them as a part of my final project for the full stack course.

Independent Work

The Shortcut, Helsinki

2022-2023

- 1. Successfully developed BMI Calculator Application, to encode user input and output with weight and height.
- REST API challenge- develop web-based application for 255 countries to fetch data from REST API with search button and react page router for single country page details.
- 3. Hotel reservation System web application.
- Apex fashion e-commerce website with front-end and back-end using JavaScript and Java.

Ottobock Pvt. Ltd., India

2014-2019 (Business Analyst, Business Developer, Sales & Marketing specialist

- Excellent planning and execution of B2B and B2C sales, meeting potential clients face-to-face, or through sales automated tools and getting business for the company
- Also did the training management role of designing sprints, meetings and targets setting for reaching business roles.
- Managed project budgets, expenditures, procurements and projections.
- Partnered with teams to guide quality and process improvements.
- Utilised creative thinking and innovative approaches involving multiple technologies.
- Tracked change order requests and financial impact on project.
- Developed analytics to identify areas for improvement and change.
- Summarised information from dataset with narratives, graphs and charts.
- Managed support exceptions and escalations, creating new or refining existing business processes.
- Supported initiatives that focused on meeting and growing business needs.
- Examined technology trends to identify markets for future product development.

EDUCATION

The Shortcut Spark Academy, Helsinki, Fl

Aug-Dec 2022

Full stack development program

Careerera, London, UK

Jul'22-Present

Full stack development program

Minna Learn, Helsinki, Fl

2022

Agile Certification

Bsc. Sciences, DU, India

2008-2013

Bachelor of Sciences

Master's Law and Ethics, India in Medical science-2019

